(Leonard:)- ...but she did kind of betray you.
- lnteresting.
(Sheldon:)You see betrayal in others
but not yourseIf.
(Leonard:)Going to Wheaton's party
is not betraying you.
(Sheldon:)Of course, you would have to believe that.
Evil always thinks it's doing right.
(Leonard:)Huh.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, Stormtrooper.
These are the droids you're looking for.
(Leonard:)I'm going to a party.
(Leonard:)I'm not turning R2-D2
and C-3PO over to the Empire!
(Sheldon:)Not yet.
What's gonna happen? Are you
and Bernadette gonna break up?
(Howard:)If we're going to get back together,
she's gonna have to apologize...
(Howard:)...and accept that I'm a grown man
who can make his own decisions.
Then convince your mother
to let you go into space.
(Howard:)Obviously.
(Bernadette:)I had no choice.
I had to tell his mother.
(Bernadette:)He can't go to space.
(Bernadette:)He's like a baby bird.